So, I'm working on the DP agency generative UI A2 UI in the fixed
schema A2 UI module, and I have followed the exact same code and steps
as stated in the documentation. And I have also made the flight scheme adjacent
from the A2 UI composer, and these are.
My current versions that I'm currently using,
and here it is.
And my current Lego-palette version installed is 1.69.2,
and here is my page.dsx file,
and here is my flight schema, which I have generated.
from A to UI Compasser and here is my backend file.
But the issue that I'm facing is that it says that A to UI
error which is the specific basic the
catalog is not found. So It is an issue and it needs to be
fixed. Thank you.